healthreviewcenter.com 2013-12-26

# Privacy Policy - Health advice, fitness tips, and reviews - Health Review CenterHealth advice, fitness tips, and reviews – Health Review Center

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of the website visitors and this privacy policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.

**The information we collect**

We will collect, store as well as use the following kinds of personal information:

(a) information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website (including your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views, website navigation)

(b) information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services

(c) information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us

(d) information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters

(e) any other information that you choose to send to us

**Using your personal information**

Personal information submitted to us via this website will be used for the purposes specified in the privacy policy and in relevant parts of the website.

We may take use of your personal information to:

(a) administer the website;

(b) improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;

(c) enable your use of the services available on the website;

(d) send to you goods purchased via the website, and supply to you services purchased via the website;

(e) send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you;

**International data transfers**

Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

Information which you provide may be transferred to countries which don’t have the data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the European Economic Area.

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and will be available, via the internet, around the world. We cannot stop the use or misuse of such information by others.

You expressly accept to such transfers of personal information.

**Security of your personal information**

We will take reasonable technical as well as organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

We will store all personal information which you provide on our secure (password- and firewall- protected) servers. All electronic transactions which you make to or receive from us will be encrypted  using SSL technology .

Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot ensure the security of data sent over the internet.

You are responsible for holding your password and user details confidential. We will not require you for your password (except when you log in to the website).

**Third party websites**

The website gets links to other websites. We will not be responsible for the privacy policies as well as practices of third party websites.

**Updating information**

Please let us know whether the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.

**Contact**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy as well as our treatment of your personal information, please write to us by email or by post to  _our postal address_ .
